{
    "subject": "Olivia_Spencer",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Phillip_Spaulding",
    "human_readable": "Olivia Spencer is married to Phillip Spalding.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9651790857315063,
            "question": "Is there a relationship between Olivia Spencer and Phillip Spalding?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9233558177947998,
            "question": "Name the person married to Phillip Spalding."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9095742702484131,
            "question": "To whom is Phillip Spalding married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8967348337173462,
            "question": "Who is married to Phillip Spalding?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.887835681438446,
            "question": "Who is Olivia Spencer married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8856220245361328,
            "question": "Is Phillip Spalding married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6614115834236145,
            "question": "What is the name of Phillip Spalding's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6423383951187134,
            "question": "What is the name of Phillip Spalding's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6420424580574036,
            "question": "Who is Olivia Spencer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5295378565788269,
            "question": "What is Olivia Spencer's marital status?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Olivia Spencer is married to Phillip Spalding.",
            "html": "yago_25013_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Olivia Spencer?",
            "html": "yago_25013_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Phillip Spalding's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_25013_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Phillip Spalding's wife?",
            "html": "yago_25013_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25013_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25013_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25013_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25013_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25013_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25013_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25013_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25013_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25013_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25013_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me explain why.  Multiple documents clearly state that Olivia Spencer and Phillip Spaulding are married. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents provide information that supports this triple. Specifically, document 11.txt and 26.txt mention that Olivia Spencer (formerly Lewis, Spaulding & O'Neill) has a child with Phillip Spaulding, named Emma Spencer Spaulding, who was born in secret due to Lizzie's resentment towards the pregnancy. This implies that Olivia Spencer is indeed married to Phillip Spalding, at least for some period of time."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Olivia Spencer is married to Phillip Spaulding.\" Specifically, it mentions multiple instances where Olivia and Phillip are depicted as being involved in each other's lives and having a relationship, including their marriage."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}